So I've got the lid piece.
Now that it's set up a little bit, set on the wheel again.
And it is rather hard.
And the first thing I'm going to do is just take my needle tool and make this top rim a little flat, so that it'll connect really easily to the other piece.
And then I'm going to take my scoring tool, get the rim wet.
And I've got my needle tool here, so you can see you don't have to have a scoring tool.
Just go back and forth and get that nice and scratched up.
Set this aside, get the base and put it on the wheel head.
And I need to turn this one eighty.
The bat pins are not always drilled perfectly on center.
So if it feels like it's off center, just turn your bat a hundred and eighty degrees.
And I'm going to do the same thing here.
I'm going to cut a little piece off to make the top nice and flat.
And I'm going to wet this and score it up.
And now I'm ready to connect these two pieces together.